

mark.nolledo@gmail.com

+63 905 399 9038

Noveleta, Cavite Philippines 4105

ABOUT

A Computer Science degree holder that has the skills and experience of a web programmer and a people-oriented service crew. Armed with technical and interpersonal skills, I could work well with any team and take on a variety of tasks.

SKILLS

Web Programming

Frontend development

- Node.JS, Webpack usage and configurations
- JavaScript frameworks such as Angular Vue for progressive web app development
- Ionic Framework 3 and 5 for cross-platform mobile apps
- Incorporation of CSS frameworks, UI and design toolkits
- API integration in frontend pages

Backend development

- Laravel and Lumen for PHP-based API development
- Django for Python-based API development
- Express for JavaScript-based API development
- Sequelize, Eloquent ORMs
- ERD design, normalization, query composition
- API testing tools such as Postman

Project Deployment and Maintenance

- Docker installation and configuration
- Shared server setup via YAMLs and Git postreceives
- Kubernetes pods deployment and configuration
- Usage of FTP and SSH for remote server access

Information Technology, Clerical, and Multimedia

- Microsoft Office and Google Suite
- Remote access tools such as TeamViewer
- Remote meeting tools such as Google Meet, Zoom
- IM platforms such as Discord, Slack, Teams
- Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign
- Figma and Adobe XD for prototyping
- Basic network security protocols

EVENTS

February 6, 2019

HackForGov: CERT-PH Cyber Security Challenge **Department of Information and Communications** Technology (DICT)

Team finalist, national; an intercollegiate cybersecurity challenge held by the DICT and CERT-PH

February 23, 2019 - February 24, 2019

Bluehacks 2019 Ateneo de Manila University

Team participant; an intercollegiate hackathon organized by AdMU with the goal of designing a self-care game.

EDUCATION

Graduate, 2014 - 2019

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Cavite State University - CCAT Campus

- Club Head, Programming Club
- Worked with SM Rosario for a joint project through the campus administration and college department
- Participated in an interuniversity and a national competition for college students
- Former layout artist for school publication

Undergraduate, 2011 - 2012

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Adamson University

EXPERIENCE

Web Programmer, May 2022 - April 2024

Ole Elite Software Philippines, Inc. Rosario, Cavite, Philippines

Involved with the development, maintenance, and deployment of web applications, development and integration of REST APIs, and server configurations.

Part-time College Instructor, February 2022 - June 2024

Cavite State University - CCAT Campus Rosario, Cavite, Philippines

Teaches Computer Science subjects, tasked with technical critic advisory duties for thesis groups, and provides assistance to students through consultations.

Web Programmer, January 2021 - April 2022

Dynamic Markups IT Solutions Inc. Rosario, Cavite, Philippines

Helpdesk Technician I, July 2020 - November 2020

Stefanini Philippines Inc. Pasay, Metro Manila, Philippines

Junior Software Engineer, June 2019 - May 2020

LEENTech Network Solutions, Inc. Tanza, Cavite, Philippines

CERTIFICATIONS

March 2019

Civil Service Eligible - Professional **Civil Service Commission - Philippines**

> Piqued your interest? Let's connect.



August 27, 2021

Prof. Noel A. Sedigo

Campus Administrator Cavite State University - General Trias City Campus Vibora, General Trias City, Cavite 4107

Dear Professor Sedigo,

I am writing to you in reference to the job posting for instructors/lecturers from your campus. Having reviewed what the campus is looking for, I believe that I may be a suitable candidate for the position.

I took Computer Science and graduated from Cavite State University - Rosario Campus, and as a student, I was able to perform well and contributed to our campus's reputation within the local and national community. We participated in programming competitions such as Hack4Gov - Cybersecurity Competition held by the Department of Information and Communications Technology, and in Bluehacks 2019, a hackathon competition held by Ateneo de Manila University. SM City Rosario also partnered with our campus where I and some of my schoolmates developed a tabulation system for two of their in-mall events last 2018, earning our department a generous deal from the mall for our efforts. And during my graduating year, I was appointed as club head for our department's Programming Club. As a result, I was able to showcase my programming skills as well as hone my interpersonal skills.

My former position as a junior software engineer at LEENTech Network Solutions, Inc. exposed me to how the I.T. industry works: communicating with clients, using different software development techniques and technologies, and collaborating with coworkers to effectively conquer a given problem. As their employee, I was able to be a part of multiple projects, presented updates and progress to clients, and provided quality output and insights for development. My one year experience with them may be short but it greatly improved my current skill set, both in technical and interpersonal aspects.

With my eagerness to do things, passion in sharing the knowledge with others, and industry experiences, I believe that this position will further help improve myself which in turn would help me improve and make an impact to the lives of other people.

For your convenience, I have included my resumé along with this letter. You may reach me by mobile phone and by email, both of which are listed below.

Thank you for considering my application. I look forward to the opportunity to speak with you in person.

With best regards,

Mark Edriane F. Nolledo

Email: mark.nolledo@gmail.com

Mobile: 0905 399 9038

August 27, 2021

Prof. Noel A. Sedigo

Campus Administrator Cavite State University - General Trias City Campus Vibora, General Trias City, Cavite 4107

Dear Professor Sedigo,

I am writing to you in reference to the job posting for instructors/lecturers from your campus. Having reviewed what the campus is looking for, I believe that I may be a suitable candidate for the position.

I am a graduate of Computer Science from Cavite State University - Rosario Campus, and while I may not be an honor student, I was able to perform admirably during my college days and contributed to our campus's reputation within the local and national community. We participated in programming competitions such as Hack4Gov - Cybersecurity Competition held by the DICT, and in Bluehacks 2019, a hackathon competition held by Ateneo de Manila University. SM City Rosario also partnered with our campus to develop a tabulation system for two of their in-mall events last 2018, earning our department a generous deal from the mall for our efforts. During my graduating year, I was appointed as club head for our department's Programming Club.

Having worked formerly as a junior software engineer at LEENTech Network Solutions, Inc., I was exposed to how the I.T. industry works: communicating with clients, software development techniques and technologies, and collaboration with coworkers to effectively conquer a given problem. As their employee, I was able to be a part of multiple projects, presented updates and progress to clients, and provided quality output and insights for development. My one year experience with them may be short, but that exposure is more than enough to further improve my current skill set, both in technical and personal aspects.

With my eagerness to do things, passion in sharing the knowledge with others, and industry experiences, I believe that this position will further help improve myself which in turn would help me improve the lives of other people.

For your convenience, I have included my resumé along with this letter. You may reach me by mobile phone and by email, both of which are listed below.

Thank you for considering my application. I look forward to the opportunity to speak with you in person.

With best regards

Mark Edriane F. Nolledo

Email: mark.nolledo@gmail.com

Mobile: 0905 399 9038